Imagine a world where the sky is always painted red and gold during sunset.
A place where volcanoes erupt continuously, spewing out thick clouds of sulfuric acid.
Welcome to Venus, the scorching hot twin sister of Earth.
The average temperature on Venus reaches as high as 462 degrees Celsius, making it the hottest planet in our solar system.
That's even hotter than the surface of Mercury, which orbits closer to the sun.
But what's most surprising is that Venus was once thought to be a potential habitable world.
New research suggests that the planet may have had liquid water on its surface just 700 million years ago.
Who knows, maybe there's still life lurking beneath those thick clouds?
Venus is full of mysteries waiting to be uncovered.
Want to learn more about this scorching hot world?
Check out our link in bio for more fascinating facts and theories!